Previously on Heated Rivalry...
So, Lily's just a buddy?
-What?
-Yo, chill out, man.
I know you text
some girl named Lily.
I don't.
Are you seeing
anyone these days?
Nope.
-I'm sorry. I can't do this.
-Hollander...
-Well, you just seem tense.
-I'm fine.
Shut up.
You're in love with him.
I'm not in love with him.
-You are.
-Fuck!
-Roz, you gotta see this.
-No!
Dude, she's, like,
a huge fucking movie star.
I'm Rose, by the way.
They are definitely
one hot couple.
They are fire.
Hey.
Hey. I have to get back
to my hotel for my pickup.
Right.
Listen, uh,
about last night, I...
It's fine.
I think this season
is stressing me out
more than usual.
Yeah. Let's do dinner
this week.
Maybe just the two of us?
Yeah, for sure.
Bye.
Top of the morning!
You, uh...
You get any sleep
last night, huh?
You're a fucking beautician.
Let's go.
All right, welcome back
to Man in the Crease,
your one-stop hockey shop.
And to the upcoming
All-Star Game in Tampa Bay...
Major League Hockey fans
are finally getting
what they've been
asking for for years:
East versus West.
Which means a chance
for something
we've never seen before:
Shane Hollander and Ilya Rozanov
playing on the same team,
maybe even the same line.
Who's centering who in Florida?
And where does Scott Hunter
fit into the mix?
And speaking of Scott Hunter,
will the New York captain
keep up his red-hot pace,
or will he...
How do we put this kindly?
Crash and burn, like he does
halfway through every season?
Not sure that's very kind,
but it was succinct.
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
You're so cute.
Have I told you
how cute you are?
No. I mean, maybe.
Well, you are.
Miles is extremely jealous.
Of me?
No, of me.
Oh! Oh.
Did you not notice
that Miles is gay?
I guess I hadn't really
thought about it, so...
Well, he is.
And he's low-key
in love with you.
Oh.
Does it surprise you
that Miles is gay?
No. I mean,
of course not, no.
Well, a lot of actors are.
They're just not all out.
Are there any, like,
gay hockey players?
I mean, yes.
Obviously, there are, but are
there any openly gay players?
Yeah, uh, no.
I mean, yeah, there are probably
gay players or whatever,
but none that have
said it publicly.
Huh.
What?
Sorry, I don't think I'm
going about this the right way.
Um...
Going about what?
I really like you, Shane.
I like you too.
But I have a feeling that...
maybe I'm not doing it for you?
Yes, you are.
-I know you like talking to me.
-Yeah.
-Do you like kissing me?
-Sure.
Wow.
No. No, no,
of course I do. Sorry.
No, hey, don't apologize.
I just...
I have a feeling.
And... and maybe I'm completely
off base here,
but I don't know, I feel like
maybe you'd rather be kissing...
Miles?
Hey it's... it's really OK.
It's not.
I do like you. I really do.
I like talking with you.
I like being with you.
I like all of it.
I know the sex stuff
is a problem, but...
It's not a problem.
A problem is
something you can fix.
We're more like
a square peg in a round hole.
Ew.
No. I'm sorry.
Forget I said that. Um...
We're just...
We're not meant to fit.
And it's really fine.
I just don't think
that we can keep trying.
I get it. I... I just, uh...
I think, um...
I think, uh...
Hey, you don't owe me
any explanation.
-I feel like I kind of do.
-You really don't.
Can I ask if you've ever
been with another guy?
Have you ever told
anyone that before?
Was it different with a guy?
Of course.
Was it better?
Yeah, it was, uh...
Um...
It was better.
The thing is, I...
I kind of prefer being the hole
rather than the peg.
Wow!
That is the best thing
any gay boyfriend of mine
has ever told me.
Oh, you've had other...
Oh, I was in theater school.
Like, 70% of my boyfriends
have left me for other guys.
-70%?
-Actually, 80%.
Yeah.
Wow.
You should follow Miles
back on Instagram.
No.
I mean, not "no,"
but I just need to sort
some things out first.
Of course.
And I was kidding about Miles,
but he totally would.
Like, in a heartbeat.
You haven't said anything
to him, have you?
No, definitely not.
And I never will.
Let's be friends.
-Yeah.
-No, seriously.
Not some bullshit,
"Let's stay friends," thing.
Let's be real friends.
Like, best friends.
OK.
I really like you, Shane.
You're secretly one of
the funniest guys I know.
Well, that secret,
you don't have to keep.
Oh, I will tell everyone.
I have a feeling that
there's not a lot of people
you can talk to.
I mean about all
the other things and stuff.
Things and stuff
can be tricky for me.
Text me whenever, OK?
I mean it, because I will be
texting you all the time.
Promise.
You will wish you never met me.
Impossible.
Matheson on the power play
while Petrov warms the bench.
Jesus Christ.
Since when do you care
what Colorado does?
Since when did you
start smoking again?
I haven't started again.
Just every once in a while.
I care about all hockey teams
as you well know.
Of course.
Especially ones that
put good Russian players
on the second shift
of the power play
so mediocre Canadian players
can waste a minute and a half
with the man advantage.
Mediocre? Matheson?
Yes. You can quote me.
When I see him
at the all-star game.
So embarrassing
that he's playing.
The people voted.
They love him.
The people are wrong.
You're playing on the same team
as Hollander this year, right?
Is he also mediocre?
No, he's amazing. Those hands.
And he's gorgeous.
If you say so.
What?
You know he's gorgeous.
And you know he's good.
He's very good.
I would love to see you
on a line with him.
Not sure he can play wing.
But you can.
You would have him center me?
Me?
The people would love it.
The people are wrong!
Ah!
I wonder how many outfits
Rose Landry will bring.
She has such good style.
Can I offer you
something to drink?
I'll have the same
as my teammate, please.
Of course.
So, what, are they out
of ginger ale, Captain?
I'm feeling a bit wild.
So this should be fun, huh?
I've always wondered
what it would be like
to play on the same team.
Have you?
Yeah, I have.
Nice that it's in Florida
this year, right?
Yes.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Did, uh, did you
bring anyone with you?
Uh, my parents
thought about coming,
but they're going to Mexico
in, like, two weeks,
and they've been
to these before, so...
Ah.
Also, I didn't feel like
being managed this weekend.
Did you, uh, bring anybody?
Nope.
Nice shirt.
Thanks. I like to, you know,
get into the spirit.
You're pulling it off.
Cats and dogs!
Look at this!
Fucking beauties!
Yeah, should be a fun time.
Careful with this guy, though.
You can never trust him.
One black coffee, please.
I'm just fucking with you, Rozy.
It'll be a hell of a time.
Let's go, East boys! Woo-hoo!
I feel like we're gonna
get a lot of that
sort of thing this weekend.
It should give us a chance
to get to know each other.
Who knows what we
might have in common.
You're looking
very pretty today.
Hmm?
Different, maybe?
Someone take you shopping?
If I, um...
If I tell you something,
will you promise not to tell
anyone or make fun of me?
Well, it depends.
Seriously.
Yeah, sure.
I hired a stylist.
Fuck you.
Sorry.
Wow. Of course you did.
I shouldn't have told you.
No, no.
I love it. I love it.
You got, what,
tired of looking like shit?
I didn't look like shit.
I just wore,
like, athletic stuff.
Mmm. I know what you wore.
And some of the guys in
the league are so fashionable.
Yeah, so very.
Not you.
Some of the guys.
In the league?
Other players, not you.
OK.
So, this has nothing to do
with Rose Landry?
No.
Well, I mean, yeah, she always
dressed, um, very well,
and so do her friends, but...
I just wanted to stop looking
like I was always
going to the gym.
I never really
cared about clothes.
So, uh, you and her are not...
We're not.
She's great, but, uh...
We're just not...
compatible, I guess.
Hmm.
I should circulate, I guess.
Yeah.
You have new clothes
to show off.
OK, and I will not
be losing this time.
But if I lose,
I will buy you all candy bars
from machine inside, OK?
Hey, Hollander!
Hollander, make sure none of
these cheaters cheat, OK?
OK.
-You know that guy?
-Yeah.
Who's this guy?
That's Shane Hollander.
Ah, so you know this guy.
He's the best player
in the league.
Oh, no, no.
That's not true.
Flesher! Boo!
No, you get out of the pool.
No, who is your dad?
Show me your dad.
OK, I forgive you.
You can stay.
On your mark, get set...
Go!
There is a shark in the water!
There is a shark!
Ah!
Great pass.
Great goal.
OK, you guys won
fair and square.
Hey, Hollander.
Can you give these
kids some money?
I don't have my wallet.
Found you.
So you were looking for me?
Of course not.
Oh, I looked up that word,
uh, "compatible."
What?
Compatible.
I thought I knew what it meant,
but I wanted to be sure.
Oh.
So, you and Rose Landry
are not...
Yeah, not compatible.
Not in that way, anyway.
When do you fly out?
Early.
Same. Columbus.
Toronto.
What room are you in?
This looks serious.
It's not.
I mean, yeah, I guess.
Can you just sit down
or something?
It's not just me, right?
Not just you, what?
You feel it too, don't you?
Feel what?
Last time we were together,
it was different.
What was different?
That you ran away?
Look, I'm... I'm sorry
I freaked out, OK?
Freaked out over nothing.
It wasn't nothing.
Don't act like that.
This is hard enough without
you being an asshole.
What do you want, Hollander?
We get together, we fuck.
It's simple.
Simple?
It's simple for me.
Bullshit!
I think...
I think I'm gay.
Hmm. Oh yeah?
What... what makes you think that?
Fuck you, you're not gay.
No, not completely.
Yeah, well, I think I am.
Completely.
OK, so you're gay, so what?
Well, it's kind of a big deal.
To me, at least.
Sorry if I'm being boring again.
Why are you telling me this?
Who else am I gonna tell?
It's... not just being gay.
It's you.
It's this.
Being gay is one thing,
but this fucking your arch-rival
is another thing.
That's why it is a secret.
I know that, but last time...
And for the record,
I am sorry about last time, OK?
I'm sorry I freaked out.
But before that...
it was nice.
It was.
And it felt like
we were something.
We can't be
something, Hollander.
Would you want to be,
if we could?
We can't.
That's not what I asked.
What does it fucking matter?
I don't think
I can keep pretending
I don't like you anymore.
You don't like me.
Yeah, I do.
I think I like you
maybe a little too much.
Don't. Don't fucking
do this, Hollander.
I'm not...
I wouldn't be able
to go home again.
Ever.
Do you get that?
Because your family?
Because Russia!
I would not be able
to go back to Russia!
What would happen to you?
I don't want to find out.
But would your parents...
My father is police.
My brother is police.
And your mother?
Dead.
I'm sorry.
I was young.
My father is very old fashioned.
And sick.
Sick like crazy?
That too, a little,
but no, sick more like...
Oh, like cancer?
Dementia.
That's awful.
Hey.
Hey...
Sorry.
What?
Nothing.
Good night, Shane.
Good night, Ilya.
Boston Lily's texting you.
Have fun!
-It's not...
-I don't care!
My brother.
You can take it if you want to.
No, I don't want to.
Is everything OK at home?
Your father?
Enough, OK?
Enough what?
Questions. You have
too many of them.
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
I wasn't clear.
I'm sorry in advance
for tonight's game.
We're gonna destroy you guys.
Oh. So you are the asshole.
No, it's still you.
No, not me.
You are the asshole.
Everyone must know this.
Everyone, Shane Hollander
is an asshole.
OK, listen up.
The rumors are true!
$1,000 for every goal
scored tonight.
OK, boys? Montreal
goes home crying.
Please, please!
You fucking heard him, boys.
Let's go, boys!
Let's do it!
Roll out!
No, no, no, it's not true.
I said you fuckers owe me $1,000
for every goal I score.
You each owe me
3,000 fucking dollars.
Fuck off, Rozy.
You all agreed, huh?
What the fuck do you want?
Hey!
Hey, did you hear about Rozanov?
What about Rozanov?
Well, he did not fly with the
rest of the team to Nashville.
He flew separately?
He did not go to
Nashville at all.
Well, he didn't get hurt
last night, did he?
-Not that I know of.
-No, he didn't.
Maybe he's sick.
He's not.
I mean, he didn't seem sick.
Who gives a shit?
ESPN is just saying
he did not go to Nashville.
Calm down.
Hi. This is Ilya.
I will never listen
to your voicemail.
Hey. Are you OK?
You wear glasses?
Just for reading.
Where are you?
Home. Put them
back on, please.
Boston?
Moscow.
Oh. Are you OK?
I will be better when I
see you in your glasses again.
Happy?
Happier.
Is your father...
Yes, dead.
Ilya...
I'm so sorry.
What are people saying about me?
Nothing.
Um, the media
is being super secretive,
and the Raiders haven't...
Good.
I will be back
by the end of the week.
You should take
more time than that.
Why? So you can catch up
to me in the scoring race?
I'm being serious.
You know,
you can talk to me
about whatever.
I want to help if I can.
Take off your clothes.
What?
I'm also being serious.
If you want to help me,
take your clothes off.
Glasses back on.
Stop fucking avoiding me.
If only.
So?
So what?
Don't fucking touch me.
Then tell me the fucking plan.
Jesus Christ.
I don't know yet, Alexei!
He just died.
Can I get a minute to breathe?
And me?
What about me?
Do I get to breathe too?
Or is that just something
reserved for rich faggots
who abandon their families?
Abandoned?
Who's money do you live on,
you piece of shit?
Who puts food in your mouth
and coke up your nose?
I have a child, Ilya!
And a fucking wife!
And me, I've spent
the last five months
taking care of our dying father
every fucking day!
I thought I heard singing.
Great.
Now we have to listen to this
whore run her mouth.
Stop, Ilya! Stop.
He's not worth it.
He's not worth anything.
You can have my apartment.
And there will be a trust
for my niece.
She can have it when she's 18.
And you will never,
ever contact me again.
If you do, I will use every
piece of my fame and money
and notoriety to make sure
that you can't show your face
in this fucking city
without someone
wanting to break it open.
So take what I offer,
shut your fucking mouth
and walk away.
I don't deserve you.
Yes, you do.
But you don't want me.
You know I love you.
I know you do.
But it's not the same
as it is with Jane, is it?
I love you too.
And whatever you need,
I'll be here.
I'm not going anywhere.
I just hope Jane
knows how lucky he is.
Hey, I'm just gonna...
Have fun!
How are you?
OK.
Not good.
Probably bad.
How's your, uh, family?
At their worst.
My brother is...
I don't know. Scared.
It makes him terrible.
And it makes me terrible back.
Is it very upsetting?
Yes.
But maybe I'm upset
about the wrong thing.
You mean not your father?
Maybe...
I...
I wish it could be different.
I wish he could know me, or...
I don't know. I don't know.
English is too hard right now.
I wish I spoke Russian.
Mmm.
Yeah, you could probably
learn it in a week.
No accent. Perfect.
Bonjour.
That's French, Ilya.
Yeah, I know, Shane.
Where are you?
I'm just walking.
I needed to get out.
Hey, uh, I have an idea.
How about you tell me
everything that's on your mind,
but in Russian?
I won't understand,
but maybe it'll help.
OK.
I never want to
come back here again.
I fucking hate it here.
And they all fucking hate me.
I pay for everything.
I make sure everyone
has clothes they like.
I make sure the food is perfect,
that Father is buried
next to his parents,
that the tomb is perfect.
And the only fucking word
I ever hear is:
"I want more, Ilya.
I need more, Ilya,
more, more, more!"
And I have nothing
for these people!
I give them everything...
but I feel fucking empty.
They don't care.
They look at me and they
see a bank. Or an enemy.
Or I don't even know what.
My brother, he always hated me.
And I know why, but...
it kills me.
And it kills me that he took
care of my father and I didn't.
But I couldn't!
I wasn't here.
I still paid for it all.
And he will never forgive me.
For any of it.
For existing.
And it means.
I have no one now.
Well, not no one. I have...
Svetlana.
She loves me.
And I love her.
But not like...
Fuck me.
But not like I love you.
That's the worst fucking part
of all this is...
that all I want is you.
It's always you.
I'm so in love with you,
and I don't know
what to do about it.
OK, I'm done.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
Thank you.
Maybe you could
teach me Russian someday.
Yeah. OK.
Only useful phrases.
Like what?
I don't know, like:
"Harder, please. Yes, sir."
Fuck you.
No, more like:
"Fuck me, please."
How about...
"I wish you were here
right now"?
I wish I was too.
A little winter thaw
couldn't come at a better time
for a Montreal team
that needs to heat up right now.
The Metros are clinging to a
wild card spot in the playoffs.
And tonight, they're facing
the Boston Raiders
with Ilya Rozanov back in action
following the passing
of his father.
Everyone's thoughts and prayers
go out to the Boston captain,
who can't have
had an easy couple of weeks.
But counting him out
would be a mistake.
It sure would.
'Cause few players respond
to adversity like Rozanov.
We still on
for tonight? After?
1919.
That's the code.
For the front door.
I'll text it to you.
Front door. Brave.
Fuck you.
Later.
What was that about?
Oh, I just offered
my condolences.
Oh, yeah. That's nice.
Fuck, I should have done that.
What did he say?
Told me to fuck off.
Jesus, what a dick.
He's not that bad.
It's mostly an act.
A pretty convincing one.
Yeah, well, let's make sure
we win this one, right?
Fucking rights!
Marleau, you motherfucker!
You hate to see that happen.
It looked like a clean hit.
Hollander just
did not see it coming.
Ilya Rozanov still on the ice,
looking very concerned.
Not even Rozanov wants to see
someone hurt like that.
Here come the medics.
It's unclear
if he's responsive or not.
One, two, three.
Is he OK? Fucking tell me!
Get to your bench, Rozanov.
I'm not gonna tell you again.
You know, you can say what
you will about this rivalry,
these two have played...
Obviously, a lot of
admiration there.
I need you to stay awake,
OK, Shane?
Eyes open, buddy.
OK. My parents...
Your parents, your coach
is calling them, OK?
OK.
Tell him I'm fine, I'm OK.
Tell who?
He's gonna worry.
Your coach is calling your dad.
Not him, Ilya.
Who? Hey, Shane, you really
need to keep your eyes open, OK?
Ilya!
I, um, I just wanted to...
Are you OK?
Concussion and
a fractured collarbone.
Out for the playoffs, but...
-Could have been worse.
Marleau feels terrible.
He did not mean to hurt you.
I know. Part of the game.
We all get our bell rung
eventually, right?
Right.
Hey.
-Hey!
-OK, OK...
Shhh, shhh.
Yes! Better.
Mmm.
You scared me.
I'm sorry I didn't
text you last night.
No, it's OK.
I was excited about last night.
I'm mostly mad at Marleau
for fucking that up.
He feels really bad.
You know, I had a whole
plan to ask you something.
Maybe it's better
if you just rest now.
-I was gonna ask you...
-Hollander...
Will you come
to my cottage this summer?
Don't go to Russia.
Come to my house.
We'll have so much fun.
It's so private.
No one will know.
Hollander, you know
I can't do that.
We could have
a week or even two.
We'd be completely alone.
Together.
Maybe. Maybe.
Oh, no.
Uh-oh!
You're not gonna
smother him with a pillow,
are you, Mr. Rozanov?
Ah, no. No, no, no.
But good thinking.
But no, I was just leaving.
OK, bye-bye.
Goodbye.
Mmm. See you next season.
Get well soon, Hollander.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Hello!
-Hello!
-Ah!
It's still in a sling,
but I can lose the thing
in a few days, I think.
How's jerking off?
Ma'am, I'm at my
parents' house, so...
So, constant? Endless?
Pretty much.
Um, how are the reshoots going?
Fine.
I mean, this movie
makes no sense.
It doesn't!
At least you're getting paid
properly this time.
I miss being kidnapped.
I regret shapeshifting.
My parents keep asking
if you're gonna
come by this summer.
Well, I still might!
They can't keep me here
till September.
I'm gonna lose my mind.
I don't think that's
what they mean.
Well, just tell them.
-Rose...
-Just do it.
Tell them I'm gay and you
got sick of being my beard.
I can't lie to them.
Um...
More than I already have.
I think they'd love it.
And then they'd have
to keep my secret.
My big lesbian secret.
Oh, God. I wish.
Same.
They probably would love that.
Third period's starting.
Coming!
OK, I gotta go,
but let me know what you decide
about Labor Day weekend.
I will. I love you.
Rozanov coming up the right wing
with Hunter staying on him.
Rozanov tries to push past him
with no luck.
He's playing hurt.
It's his ribs, I bet.
-How do you know that?
-Am I right?
I don't know.
Your mother's a witch.
OK, the Raiders have lost.
Dinner to celebrate.
-Dad!
-What?
We don't hate him anymore?
I can't keep up!
No, we do, just...
Rosanov went to see Shane
in the hospital.
Oh, so now you like him.
Well, now I hate him less.
And good for Scott Hunter.
Why good for Scott Hunter?
I don't know.
It's his year.
How can you possibly know that?
-She's a witch!
-Stop it with that.
-Or what?
-Or I'll cast a spell.
Turn off all the lights
when you go to bed.
And stop staring at the screen.
My head is fine,
and I'm a fully grown adult.
And in less than one minute,
ladies and gentlemen,
the New York Admirals will have
done what they set out to do,
finally bringing the Cup
back to New York.
After over a decade
in the wilderness,
Scott Hunter
and his teammates taking...
I told you!
Who are you texting?
Hayden.
Oh, how's the baby?
Great!
...is finally
making history tonight.
Fifteen seconds remaining.
Marleau holds it behind the net.
Ten seconds remaining
as Marleau passes it.
They're running out the clock.
The New York crowd
is on its feet.
They can't believe it!
And there you have it!
82 regular season games,
23 playoff performances,
and the New York Admirals
have won the Cup
for the first time in 28 years!
Your 2017 champions!
They've done it!
I cannot believe it.
I cannot believe what
I am witnessing right now!
Your champions
are the New York Admirals!
The 2017 Champions!
Yeah!
Hey...
I'm not sad.
You're allowed to be.
Yes! Let's fucking go, bro!
We fucking did it, baby!
Yeah!
Vaughn takes it from Hunter.
Vaughn was drafted six...
♪ Give me your eyes ♪
♪ I need sunshine ♪
♪ Your blood, your bones ♪
♪ Your voice... ♪
And winning the show
is getting to bring
the people you love...
For your niece. Don't forget.
Put them in the suitcase.
Incredible scene down here
as the Cup is passed around.
Hunter seems to be
looking out to the fans.
No doubt a recognition
of their sticking with him.
♪ But I'll believe in anything ♪
♪ And you'll believe
in anything ♪
♪ I said I'll believe
♪ And you'll believe
in anything ♪
Yeah, you. Come!
Go!
♪ If I could get the fire out
from the wire ♪
♪ I'd share a life
and you'd share a life ♪
Is that a fan?
Big moment for that fan if true.
♪ If I could get the fire out
from the wire ♪
♪ I'd take you
where nobody knows you ♪
♪ And nobody gives a damn ♪
♪ I said nobody knows you ♪
Hunter now trying to
get someone's attention,
apparently inviting someone
from the crowd down to the rink.
He just hopped the boards.
-You don't have to do this.
-Yes. Yes, I do.
♪ And I could
give you my apologies ♪
♪ By handing over
all the olive trees ♪
♪ And I could take away
the shaky knees ♪
♪ And I could give you
all the olive trees ♪
♪ Oh, look at the trees
and look at my face ♪
♪ And look at a place
far away from here ♪
♪ So give me your eyes ♪
♪ I need sunshine ♪
♪ Give me your eyes ♪
I love you so fucking much.
I love you too.
Oh, wow!
You don't see that every day.
Pretty big night for hockey.
-And listen to that crowd!
-They're loving this!
Good for him!
Good for Scott Hunter!
What the...
I'm coming to the cottage.
Uh...
♪ Nobody knows you ♪
♪ And nobody gives
a damn either way ♪
♪ You know I'll believe
in anything ♪
♪ And you'll believe
♪ Because nobody knows you ♪
♪ And nobody gives
a damn either way ♪
Closed Captions: MELS